Mr. Fan
I heard you're a retired professor
with very high academic standing
so I have a few questions to ask you
You've heard about that?
Bring it here, let me see
Here, this one
You're Yingzi, right?
Hello
You can ask me questions too, you know
You don't have to ask him
Ask you?
Are you up to it?
Yeah, President Li
This is in English
Do you understand it?
I don't understand?
Yeah right
When I went to India for business back then
even the beggars there understood English
President Li
Then tell us
what this means
The meaning of this paragraph is...
Why should I tell you?
Didn't you say you understood?
Do I have to tell you just because I understand?
Is that so?
If you can translate
this sentence
I'll give you one hundred yuan
Deal?
Deal
The meaning of this passage is
Heaven gave me talent for a reason
And a mouse's son can dig a hole
I earned this hundred bucks easily
Come back, come back
Put it down
I earned this hundred bucks
You translated it wrong
Why are you taking it?
You just said
you'd pay a hundred if I translated it
You didn't say I had to translate it correctly
Bye-bye now
You're cheating
Give it to me
Give me the money
Xiaolan
Where have you been?
I went shopping
Zhongguancun No. 1 was really lively
How can you go shopping during work hours?
What are you doing?
Did you give Gou'er Ye his medicine today?
I actually forgot about that
How could you forget that?
If Dr. Chang finds out
How could he possibly know?
If he finds out
it means you snitched
Me?
Gou'er Ye, time for your medicine.
Okay.
Here.
You take it.
What?
It's not for me.
It's for you.
Don't be polite, I'm not hungry.
You have to take it.
What for?
This isn't medicine.
It's chocolate.
I won't take medicine if you don't give me chocolate.
For an old man your age,
why are you so greedy?
Fine, here you go.
Here.
Xiaolan.
How can you give him chocolate?
This is my chocolate.
Gou'er Ye.
You have diabetes.
You can't eat sweets.
You must never give him sweets again.
Or it could be dangerous.
Then what should I do?
Without chocolate,
this old man won't take his medicine.
Figure something out.
Gou'er Ye.
Take your medicine first.
After the medicine, I'll buy you eight-treasure porridge.
Sugar-free.
Is it sweet?
It's sweet.
Come on, take the medicine first.
This medicine...
Xiaolan, did you get the wrong medicine?
Impossible.
How could I...
You really got it wrong.
Look, this is so dangerous.
Go change it immediately.
Okay.
You have to take this medicine away too.
It can't stay here.
Stand there.
Director Chang.
Has Gou'er Ye taken his medicine?
He has.
You get some rest.
Xiaofang.
It's not that I don't let you eat snacks.
But it's working hours right now.
It wasn't me.
This chocolate is...
That chocolate is for me to eat.
How could you give Gou'er Ye chocolate?
Do you know what condition he has?
I know.
He has diabetes.
You knew, yet you still gave it to him?
If he develops ketones, who's responsible?
I didn't give him chocolate.
I was trying to give him his medicine.
Just to give him medicine,
you let him eat chocolate?
What medicine is this?
Do you know you took the wrong medicine?
This is the wrong one.
This isn't for Gou'er Ye.
Xiaofang, you have disappointed me so much.
Do you know that giving a patient the wrong medicine
can be extremely dangerous?
You and Xiaolan, the two of you,
are both currently on probation.
Only one of you can stay at the center.
I originally intended to keep you.
I really didn't expect you...
Dr. Chang.
This isn't the one. Xiaofang...
took the wrong one.
It should be this bottle.
I...
Look at this.
You two came from the same place.
How can your professional skills differ so much?
Can't you learn more from Xiaolan?
Director Chang, this was actually...
Actually, I was supposed to feed Gou'er Ye.
But I heard Grandma Jin coughing just now,
so I went to check on her for Xiaofang.
I didn't expect that in just this moment...
Director Chang, please don't criticize her anymore.
She was just trying to help me out.
She can't even do her own job properly,
yet she tries to help others?
No, she meant well.
Please don't criticize her.
Xiaofang, go check on Grandma Jin.
Come back.
Dr. Chang, are there any other instructions?
Your shift leader,
Sister Niu,
has taken two weeks of sick leave.
So during this period,
the acting shift leader...
Xiaolan, you do it.
Thank you, Dr. Chang.
I, Xiaolan, promise to complete the task.
Gou'er Ye.
I'm leaving now.
Remember to take your medicine.
Take your medicine.
Xiaofang
Go check if today's delivery is here.
But I'm giving Grandma Jin her medicine.
I can't step away.
You dare disobey the boss?
If I leave,
who will watch Grandma Jin?
It's fine.
I'm here.
Then you have to be careful.
Don't let her choke.
I know, she won't.
Grandma Jin,
let me give you your medicine.
You want to sleep here?
Here.
What's wrong?
Why are you coughing?
A monk?
From which temple?
Talk about a tangent.
Hey.
What is going on here?
Royal Physician Sun, it's my fault.
I forgot to remind Xiaofang today
to suction Grandma Jin's phlegm.
What?
You got the munchies?
Who doesn't love a tasty treat?
It's such a routine procedure.
Does it need reminding?
Isn't she on probation?
She lacks experience.
It's understandable.
I'll suction Grandma Jin right now.
About this...
please don't tell Director Chang.
That won't do.
This matter...
I must report to Director Chang immediately.
What? Sleeping?
Didn't I just wake up from my nap?
Don't! I'll suction the phlegm right now.
No need.
Well...
This morning,
Xiaofang already did it for me.
You can hear again all of a sudden?
Xiaolan.
Grandma Jin, have an orange.
Why is it that
you're the one looking after Grandma Jin now?
Xiaofang said
she had to go out for something.
Here.
Hmph.
Just as I thought.
How is this couplet?
Is it neat?
Not bad, not bad at all.
Noun matches noun.
Verb matches verb.
Adjective matches adjective.
Typo matches typo.
Hey!
Why can't you say anything nice?
Hello, grandpas.
Xiaofang is here.
Is there a problem?
Do you need my advice?
No.
It's just that I'm off duty today.
I want to go into town for a walk.
Is there anything you two need to buy?
I can bring it back for you.
Then first help me...
...get an ink cartridge.
Okay.
Buy me a bottle of Zhonghua ink.
Sure.
By the way.
If you pass by a pharmacy...
...buy me a pair of those magnetic insoles.
The kind that cures foot odor.
You have foot odor?
I hadn't noticed until you mentioned it.
Who has foot odor?
I'm buying them for you.
When you take off your shoes, the smell makes me dizzy.
My feet smell?
Slander!
Xiaofang.
Buy me a magnetic herbal pillow.
The kind that treats snoring.
You snore when you sleep?
I don't snore.
He snores.
His snoring is outrageous.
Keeps me up all night.
Who snores?
You are spreading rumors.
If you don't believe me, let's listen tonight.
Then who has smelly feet?
Smell them right now.
Knock it off, don't embarrass yourself.
Grandpas, please stop arguing.
The things you want to buy...
...I've written them down.
I'll go buy them for you now.
Don't go yet.
We have to give you the money.
No need, we can settle it when I get back.
I use WeChat Pay.
It's very convenient.
Take it first.
After you buy them...
...we'll settle the difference.
Right. What if mine isn't enough?
Use Professor Fan's money to cover it.
Don't.
If his money isn't enough, don't buy it for him.
Here, take it.
Really, no need, Grandpa.
Take it.
When I get back...
How can we not give you money?
Aha!
I've caught you this time, haven't I?
Xiaofang, you have some nerve.
Daring to solicit red envelopes privately.
Who solicited red envelopes?
I can testify.
She didn't ask for it.
This red envelope is...
What red envelope?
This money is for her to buy things for us.
Giving things isn't allowed either.
Who gave things?
This money is for her...
...to buy things on our behalf.
That's right.
Grandpas.
What are you afraid of?
If there's a problem, file a complaint.
Don't worry.
She doesn't dare do anything to you.
Xiaolan, you...
...you are bullying people too much.
That's right.
Don't falsely accuse good people.
Let's go.
Come with me to reason with Director Chang.
Who are you scaring with the Director?
You think I...
...wouldn't dare?
Thinking just because someone protects you, you're fine.
Your probation is almost up.
Watch yourself.
I think you're the one who needs to be careful.
You have too many wicked schemes.
Watch out for premature beats.
I'm so pissed off.
Hello, Dr. Chang.
This is Xiaolan.
I need to report a situation.
My heart has been feeling really uncomfortable lately.
I might be having premature beats.
Who told you to be so scheming?
You... I...
Calm down.
Calm and objective.
Let's not get involved.
We'll just investigate.
No, she is just too infuriating.
Who do you think you are?
That's enough.
Xiaofang, why are you being so polite with me?
If I say take it, just take it.
I really can't.
The community has rules.
We can't accept gifts from patients.
You're not accepting it.
I'm giving it to you.
Besides, I'm not a patient.
That's still not allowed.
I say it's allowed, so it is.
My daughter brought this back from a business trip.
One box for you.
One box for Grandma Jin.
Little Li.
Is this for me?
Yes.
It sticks to my teeth.
Just give it to Xiaofang.
You see?
Grandma Jin has spoken.
Just accept it.
Try a piece first.
It's really delicious, I'm telling you.
Really, try it.
Xiaogan sesame candy.
It's my favorite.
Really?
You like it too?
That's great.
Then these two boxes...
I'm giving them to Xiaofang.
President Li...
I... I...
Grandma Jin.
Royal Physician Sun.
Come take a look, quick.
What's wrong with Grandma Jin?
Grandma Jin.
Where does it hurt?
Where are the flower buds?
Don't pick them. Wait for them to bloom.
Royal Physician Sun.
Grandma Jin is getting on in years.
For the details...
You'll have to ask Xiaofang.
Xiaofang.
Grandma Jin's...
You...
Why are you eating snacks during work hours?
I wasn't eating snacks.
This is President Li...
President Li just gave this to me.
She's just having a taste.
You're accepting gifts from an elder?
No, Royal Physician Sun...
Let me explain.
Save it. No need to explain.
I know exactly what's going on.
No, Sun...
Xiaolan, what do you have to say?
Stop right there
Where are you going?
Taking Grandma Jin out for a walk.
Did you feed her?
Yes, I did.
Did she take her medicine?
Yes, she did.
Then...
Did you take her for a walk?
Not yet.
Look.
How are you doing your job?
Isn't that what I'm doing right now?
Well...
Xiaolan.
What are you looking for?
I'm finding fault.
No.
I'm looking for an excuse.
No, not that either.
I...
I'm checking to see...
if there's any work you missed.
Oh, right.
Did you give Gou'er Ye...
a nail trim?
Did you cut his hair?
No.
Why not?
Isn't that your job?
My job?
Why can't you do it?
If I do it, does that mean you can't?
Go.
But if I go...
who will walk Grandma Jin?
I'm here.
So...
Grandma Jin.
I'm going to leave for a bit.
I'll come back to keep you company later.
Where did you buy that big watermelon?
Grandma Jin.
I'm busy.
You just...
stay here in the shade...
and cool off by yourself.
Xiaolan.
Dr. Chang, I...
I was just taking Grandma Jin for a walk.
Why are you taking care of Grandma Jin again?
Where is Xiaofang?
She went out to meet her boyfriend.
So I'm just doing a bit more to cover for her.
She found a boyfriend already?
Even if she found a boyfriend...
she shouldn't go out during work hours.
That's outrageous.
Fine, thanks for your hard work.
Little Chang, she didn't find a boyfriend.
She went to buy me a big watermelon.
Whenever this happens...
your hearing suddenly works.
I have things to do.
You just...
stay here quietly for a while.
Wait.
Wait, I...
I have an emergency.
You said this sentence is...
Grandma Jin.
Why are you here alone?
Where's the caregiver?
This is bad.
Xiaocai.
I need to use the toilet.
No problem.
I'll take you there.
Go away.
Take me where?
You, a grown man...
why are you meddling?
It's okay, no problem.
We Chinese people...
men and women keep their distance, understand?
What does that mean?
It means...
that men and women...
I'm not explaining it to you.
If I wait any longer, I won't make it.
Make...
it?
Oh dear.
What happened?
Still didn't make it.
Giving patients the wrong medicine
Snacking during work hours
Meeting your boyfriend on the clock
Soliciting red envelopes
Accepting gifts
Neglecting the elderly
Causing Grandma Jin...
Come here
Give me an explanation
I won't explain
What kind of attitude is that?
I quit
Is that good enough for you?
You think you're in the right?
I'm so furious
I'm really furious
That's how the real world is
Every workplace
has these deceitful schemers
who thrive like fish in water
No
I have to step in
I've made up my mind.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Don't go.
Don't leave!
With Xiaolan here,
I can't do this job.
Xiaofang, don't be so impulsive.
You're the joy of Changqingju.
If you leave,
the elders will be so upset.
Exactly.
Brother Yusheng, stop talking.
I...
I can't bear to leave the elders either.
Especially Grandma Jin.
She treats you like her own granddaughter.
If you go, you're dumping her on Xiaolan?
That's right.
Grandma Jin...
I feel like she's my own grandmother.
But I've already said the words.
What are you afraid of?
I'll write you a certificate tomorrow.
You get the elders to sign it.
It'll definitely work.
Childish.
That's kid stuff.
What signature?
What certificate?
None of that works.
The urgent task right now
is for Xiaofang to write a detailed,
concise,
and material-rich resignation report.
Why resign?
Lao Li, what kind of idea is that?
Isn't this
eating salt when you're thirsty,
wearing cotton when you're hot?
Yes, Grandpa President Li.
I'm still on probation.
I can just leave.
Why write a resignation report?
No.
This resignation report must be written.
Young people
must finish what they start.
Then what should I write?
First, the reason for resignation.
The process.
Then there's our Changqingju's
elders' ages,
hometowns,
medical history,
marital history,
resumes,
relationships with children,
contact information,
temperaments,
hobbies and interests,
and when nursing,
what to pay attention to.
I'm resigning,
what's the use of writing all this?
It's useful.
Listen to Grandpa.
That's right.
This child is really outrageous.
She's here. What's here?
Why are there so many people?
I get it.
Preparing to celebrate my successful employment, right?
It's all what I should do.
Look.
Under my meticulous care,
Grandma Jin's cough
is much smoother than before.
Auntie Cai's eye-rolling
is also more fresh and refined than before.
Grandpa Liang's facial twitching
is much more lively than before.
You traitor dog!
Wait for the Eighth Route Army to deal with you!
Gou'er Ye's cursing
is also more full of energy than before.
You are shameless.
Mr. Rudy too...
What are you saying?
Rudy, what he's saying is...
There are two Chinese characters
that he knows how to write.
You definitely don't know how to write.
Impossible. What characters?
Shame.
Can you write it?
Why wouldn't I know shame?
Don't worry, Xiaofang
The real culprit
We all told Dr. Chang
We all support you
Child
Don't be afraid
No matter what happens
Grandma is on your side
Right
What's that...
How do they say it nowadays?
Back you
Support you
Support and back you
No
Just
What
I couldn't hear to begin with
And you stick this lousy
lousy thing in here
Lao Li
It's all your fault
Making the kid write some resignation report
Isn't this
self-sabotage
and giving others leverage?
I really don't get you
It's not strange you don't get it
It'd be strange if you did
You haven't navigated the business world
Don't understand HR
Don't understand personnel relations
This resignation report
on the surface is a resignation report
but in reality
it's still a resignation report
Isn't that nonsense?
But the mystery lies in
this resignation report
Let me tell you
Are you listening or not?
Look
Look at you
how old are you
still doing this
Do you know what this was called in the past?
It's called eavesdropping
Honestly
Move aside, all of you
Here, let me listen too
You took it away
I've said it before
Of the two of you
only one can stay
But now
since Xiaofang voluntarily resigned
we have to make a decision early
Now I announce
Well
Comrade Wang Sufang
go prepare yourself
Understood
Tomorrow
you will be Yangliu Xincheng's
official employee
I'll just
Huh?
On what grounds?
Because based on her resignation report
and our investigation
our conclusion is
Wang Sufang is a
meticulous and enthusiastic worker
She knows every senior's condition
and characteristics
Moreover
in her resignation report
she proposed practical
and personalized care plans
Knowledgeable, capable
caring
This is exactly the most needed
most excellent nursing talent we need
Then
Then I also
Then you what?
Not getting along with such talent
logically speaking
the one with the problem
should be you
Celebrate Xiaofang's employment
Great
Didn't you always say
observe, don't intervene?
I've thought it over carefully
and the final conclusion is
to hell with it
Come on, everyone
to congratulate Xiaofang
tonight is my treat
Great
No way
You can't fight me for this
I have a '92 Maotai
Is this called
drinking celebratory wine?